Finding Aid for francisco
Clarke Historical Library
- Francisco Photography Studio Photographic Collection is open for research.
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hartley, Russell H.,undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Harton, Annette,undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Harvey, [no first name] -Copy (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hast, Donald - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hatt, Vf.,undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hatt, Lavier - 8-year-old Girl,undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Havck, Carl - 4-year-old Boy,undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Haviland, Wm. - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hayden, Jim,undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Haynes, Patty - (Girl),undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hayward, D. F. - Copy of Air Force Discharge,undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hayward, Roy - Copy of Army Discharge,undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Haywood, LeRoy - Couple and Dog,1963 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hazelton, Duane,undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hazelton, Esther,undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hazelton, Mary Lou - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hech, Barbara - (Nurse),undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Heckert, M.J.,undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Heinlein, Don - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Heinlein, William - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 5=49)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Heinlien, Robt. - Baby Girl (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Helman, Oliver - Weller, Beulah - Marriage License,undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Heushaw, Joe - 2-year-old Boy,undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hewitt, Roy -3 Boys,March 28, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hewlett, Roy - and Wife,undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hewlett, Yvonne - Copy of Marriage License,December 26, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hill, L.D. - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hills, Herbert - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hitchingham, Leo - 1-year-old Girl,undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hoas, George,undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hodgins, Harold - 4 Children,undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hoffman, David,undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hoffmeyer, Olin - Copy,February 12, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hogg, Rollie - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hogg, Rollie - Family,undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hoggart, M. - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Holley, Autumn - H.S. (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Holliday, Gladys,undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Holliday, Gladys - Girl,undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Holliday, Sally,June 24, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Holt, Diann - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Holt, Russell - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R,Hood, Herbert - Boy,undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Horn, Clarence,undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Horn, Helen - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hough, Jim - 1-year-old,September 20, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hough, Jim,May 1959 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hough, Jim - 14-month-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, House, Ed - Copy (5 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, House, Ed - Family Tree (William Marlin),July 8, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, House, Grace - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hovey, Terry,undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Howard, Clarence - Wedding - Martha Nickel,undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Howard, Richard,May 19, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Howell, C. - Baby,undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Howell, Florence,undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hoyt, Shirley - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Huber, Floyd - Family,undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Huguelet, Frank - Couple at Moose Lodge,195u? (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hunter, John - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hunter, Lyle,undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hunter, Lyle - Girl,undated (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hurbis, Helen,undated (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hutchinson, Sandra,undated (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hyde, Mary - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Hyde, Mary and Son,undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Irwin, Pam,undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Irwin, Patricia - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jackson, Floyd,undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jackson, Floyd (2 envelopes),1959 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jackson, Floyd - 3-year-old Girl,undated (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jackson, Floyd - 14-year-old Girl,undated (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jackson, Floyd - 2- and 4-year-olds,undated (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jackson, Joe, I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jackson, John, 11-month-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jackson, Sue,undated (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jackson, Terry - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jagger, Lowell - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jagger, Lowell - and wife,undated (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jarecki Manufacturing Company (3 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jarman, Glen - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jarman, Jack,undated (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jason, Laurie -1st Communion,undated (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jennings, P.L. - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jennings, Stanford - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jimenez, Jane - H.S. (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, John, Marion (Mrs.) - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Johnson, Arnold,undated (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Johnson, Harald - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Johnson, Jerry Lou,undated (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Johnson, John - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Johnston, Mark - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jones, Dick,undated (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jones, Harry - 7-month-old and 3-year-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jones, Howard,undated (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jones, Jim,undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jones, John - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jones, Lynn - and Girl,undated (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jones, Mary A.,undated (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jones, Milo - Fish (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Jones, Ted - Wedding,undated (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Joslin, Gail,undated (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Joslin, R.E., Sr. - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Joslin, Sue,undated (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kahgegab, Lorna - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kampt, H. - Wedding,undated (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kappler, Melva,undated (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Keast, George - Wedding,undated (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Keene, Duane - Copy of a Horse Race at Ionia,August 9, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Keene, Tom,undated (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kelso, [no first name] - Copy,June 22, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kennedy, John - Family,September 11, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kennedy, Phillip - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kequom, Frank - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Ketchum, John,undated (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kickey Electric Company,undated (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kierunsaari, Gerald,undated (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kile, Carol,undated (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kile, Jean - ?-month-old and Mother,undated (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kinkle, Fred,undated (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kinkle, Margaret - 6-month-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kipfmueller, Karl - (2),undated (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kipfmueller, Kate,undated (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kipfmueller, Leo - (2), 3 - month - old,undated (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kipfmueller, R.,1951 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kirvan, Otis -Mrs. and Son,undated (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Klein, Richard - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Klozik, John - Roethlisberger, Jean, Copy of Marriage License,undated (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Knake, Henrietta,undated (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kniffen, H. - 2 Babies,undated (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Knour, L. - Wedding (2 envelopes),1949 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Knour, L.,undated (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Knowlton, Sharon - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kobel, John,undated (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kornexl, J.W.,undated (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kornexl, Myrtle -1st Communion,undated (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Krell, Merne - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kuhlman, [no first name] - 4 generations (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kuhlman, Al,undated (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kuhlman, Helen,undated (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kuhlman, LeRoy - 1-year-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kuhlman, LeRoy,undated (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kullman, Betty - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kullman, Leroy -1-and 3-year-olds,undated (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kullman, Raymond,undated (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kullman, Raymond - Wedding (3 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kullman, Rosie,undated (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kunkle, Dan,undated (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kuzma, Joe,April 11, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kye, Harry C. (4 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kyser, E.,undated (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Kyser, Vern - Couple,undated (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, LaBrecque, Larry,undated (Box 2, Folder 191)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lackie, Don - 2 Children,undated (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Laidley, Mary Kay,undated (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Landon, Dorothy - Copy (3 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Landwehr, Wm. - Copy (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Larsen, Lucene,undated (Box 2, Folder 196)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lasko, John - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Latham, J. - 6-month-old Girl,August 10, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 198)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lawens, Mark - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 199)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lawens, Wm. and Wife- 50th Anniversary,April 14, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 200)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lawrence, Tom - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 201)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lawson, Jack - 1st Communion (2),undated (Box 2, Folder 202)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lawson, L.,undated (Box 2, Folder 203)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Layfield, [no first name] - Baby,undated (Box 2, Folder 204)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Layfield, Art - 2 Children (3 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 205)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Layfield, Art - Flower Girl,undated (Box 2, Folder 206)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Layfield, Art - Flower Girl and Ring Bearer,undated (Box 2, Folder 207)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lea, Chas. (Mr. and Mrs.) - Singles (2 envelopes),November 30, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 208)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Leffingwell, Harold - Copy of Marriage License,undated (Box 2, Folder 209)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Leffingwell, Harold - Wedding,undated (Box 2, Folder 210)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Left, Gerald,undated (Box 2, Folder 211)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Left, Gerald (3),undated (Box 2, Folder 212)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lehman, Dwight - 3 Babies,undated (Box 2, Folder 213)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Len, Norbert,undated (Box 2, Folder 214)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Leonard, Alfred - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 215)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Leonard, Alfred - Nine-month-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 216)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Leonard, Gale - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 217)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Leonard, Jim - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 218)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Leonard, Marge - H.S.,December 20, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 219)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lewis, Janet - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 220)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Ley, Edward - Wedding (3 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 221)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Ley, LeRoy - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 222)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lezen, Stella - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 223)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lichert, Dolph,undated (Box 2, Folder 224)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lirones, Dan,undated (Box 2, Folder 225)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lirones, Dan,1953 (Box 2, Folder 226)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lirones, Sam - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 227)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Little, Blanche - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 228)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Little, Jack -1-year-old Girl,undated (Box 2, Folder 229)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lloyd, Ada,undated (Box 2, Folder 230)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Long, Patrick - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 231)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Loomis, Betty - 2.5-year-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 232)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Loomis, Buhl, - 2 Children,undated (Box 2, Folder 233)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Loomis, R., - 1.5-year-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 234)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Loomis, Roby - Copy of Isabella County State Bank Receipt,June 12, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 235)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Loreny, Rose Marie,undated (Box 2, Folder 236)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lorenz, Mary Lou,undated (Box 2, Folder 237)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lorenz, Pete,undated (Box 2, Folder 238)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lough, Richard - Baby,undated (Box 2, Folder 239)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Love, Floyd - 2 Babies,undated (Box 2, Folder 240)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lovejoy, Pat,undated (Box 2, Folder 241)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lowther, Ed and Wife,January 8, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 242)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Luce, Clifford - and Brother,undated (Box 2, Folder 243)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lueder, Irvin (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 244)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lueder, Irvin - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 245)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lueder, Otto and Wife - Copy,April 19, 30, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 246)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lumbert, A. - Baby Boy,undated (Box 2, Folder 247)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lyon, Sandra,undated (Box 2, Folder 248)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Lyou, Udele,undated (Box 2, Folder 249)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McAlester, Joe - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 250)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McBride, Dianna - I.D.,September 11, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 251)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McBride, Nelson - 2-year-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 252)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McBride, Rachel,December 2, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 253)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McBride, Rachel, Sailors,December 2, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 254)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McCabe, Jim,undated (Box 2, Folder 255)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McCall, John - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 256)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McCann, Pete,undated (Box 2, Folder 257)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McCaul, Gerald,undated (Box 2, Folder 258)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McClintic, Shirley - I.D.,October 28, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 259)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McConnell, Chas. (Mrs.) - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 260)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McConnell, Chas. - Daughter's Wedding,undated (Box 2, Folder 261)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McConnell, Jesse,undated (Box 2, Folder 262)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McConnell, Kenneth - 2 Children,1961 (Box 2, Folder 263)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McConnell, Kenneth - Copy, Marine,undated (Box 2, Folder 264)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McCord, Gerald - 8- and 12-year-olds,undated (Box 2, Folder 265)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McCord, Jerry (7 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 266)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McCord, Jerry, 2 children,undated (Box 2, Folder 267)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McCrimmon, Betty - 2 Children,undated (Box 2, Folder 268)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McCullough, Florence - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 269)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McCullough, Ron - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 270)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, [no first name],undated (Box 2, Folder 271)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, Barbara - 2 Children 8- and 2-year-olds,undated (Box 2, Folder 272)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, Barbara - 2-year-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 273)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, Ed - 7-month-old,September 1961 (Box 2, Folder 274)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, Ed,March 12, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 275)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, Elton - 18-month-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 276)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, Elton - 1-year-old,1960 (Box 2, Folder 277)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, Frank - Family,undated (Box 2, Folder 278)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, Gerald - 7-month-old,September 21, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 279)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, John - 7-month-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 280)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, John - 8-month-old,April 23, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 281)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, John - 6-month-old,December 8, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 282)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, John - 7-month-old,July 20, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 283)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, John - 6-month-old,October 1967 (Box 2, Folder 284)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, John - 7 Children,December 9, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 285)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, Kay - 7-month-old,undated (Box 2, Folder 286)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDonald, Mike - H.S.,September 28, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 287)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDowell, M.K.,undated (Box 2, Folder 288)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDowell, M.K. - Copy,undated (Box 2, Folder 289)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McDowell, M.K. (Mrs.) - Copy (2 envelopes),June 25, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 290)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McIntosh, Ed - 2 Children (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 291)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McIntosh, Ed (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 292)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McLacklin, Mrs.,undated (Box 2, Folder 293)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McLacklin, Betty,undated (Box 2, Folder 294)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McLacklin, Maxine (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 295)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McQueen, Harol - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 296)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McQueen, Lee - Couple,undated (Box 2, Folder 297)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, McQuirk, Sue,undated (Box 2, Folder 298)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, MacGregor News Women's League Bowling Champs,December 1941 (Box 2, Folder 299)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Machuta, Hope (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 300)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Machuta, John - Girl,undated (Box 2, Folder 301)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Mahaffey, Joe - and Wife,undated (Box 2, Folder 302)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Malusek, Anne - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 303)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Manausa, Thomas - Boy,undated (Box 2, Folder 304)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Mardiny, Benny,undated (Box 2, Folder 305)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Markham, M. - Copy (2 envelopes),December 20, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 306)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Marks, Betty - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 307)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Marks, Tom, Wife I.D. and Daughter I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 308)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Marquardt, Dick,undated (Box 2, Folder 309)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Mars, Jack,undated (Box 2, Folder 310)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Martin, Harry - 3-year-old Boy,March 9, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 311)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Martin, Harry - 2-year-old Boy,March 6, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 312)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Martin, Harry - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 313)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Martin, Herbert,undated (Box 2, Folder 314)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Martin, Herman - and Wife,undated (Box 2, Folder 351)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Martin, Howard - Wedding (3 envelopes),undated (Box 2, Folder 316)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Martin, Leon,undated (Box 2, Folder 317)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Martin, Nancy - H.S.,undated (Box 2, Folder 318)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Marzke, Lloyd - Copy, Lloyd's Shoes,undated (Box 2, Folder 319)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R, Mason, Velda - I.D.,undated (Box 2, Folder 320)